Ricardo Piglia Papers, 1954-2016: Finding Aid C1513
Manuscripts Division
- Series 3: Loose Page Notes and Drafts, 1962-1997; 24 boxes
  - Subseries 3: Notes About Various Research Topics, 1971-1991; 14 boxes
    - Notas sobre lo verosímil / "El laboritorio del escritor" / Vanguardia y traducción (2 of 2), 1976-1982; 1 folder (Box B-001153, Folder 8)
    - Notas sobre Lugones (Leopoldo) y Horacio Quiroga, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001154, Folder 1)
    - Notas sobre Lugones (Leopoldo) / Nacionalismo / Populismo / Ideología, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001154, Folder 2)
    - Notas sobre Macedonio Fernández, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001154, Folder 3)
    - Notas sobre Mijaíl Bajtín / Género, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001154, Folder 4)
    - Notas sobre relación economía y política, circa 1971; 1 folder (Box B-001154, Folder 5)
    - Notas sobre Rodolfo Walsh, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001154, Folder 6)
    - Notas sobre Sarmiento / Analogía / Ficción y política, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001154, Folder 7)
    - Notas sobre Sarmiento / Civilización y barbarie, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001155, Folder 1)
    - Notas sobre Sarmiento / Civilización y barbarie / Rosas / "Autobiografía", undated; 1 folder (Box B-001155, Folder 2)
    - Notas sobre Sarmiento / Rosas, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001155, Folder 3)
    - Notas sobre traducción y literatura / Ideología / Dependencia, 1971; 1 folder (Box B-001172, Folder 5)
    - Notas sobre traducciones / Jorge Luis Borges / Roberto Arlt / Manuel Puig / Franz Kafka, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001155, Folder 4)
    - Notas sobre Walter Benjamin / El kitsch, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001155, Folder 5)
    - Sarmiento: historia y literatura (bibliografía) / Printed Materials, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001155, Folder 6)
    - Sobre el Facundo de Sarmiento / "La ficción en América Latina: el caso de la novela argentina.", undated; 1 folder (Box B-001156, Folder 1)
      Includes draft typescript of "La ficción en América Latina: el caso de la novela argentina."
    - Situación de Arlt, Borges en la literatura argentina, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001156, Folder 2)
    - Teoría, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001156, Folder 3)
    - Teoría de la ficción / Macedonio / Arlt, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001156, Folder 4)
    - Teoría de la ficción / Notas sobre la traducción, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001156, Folder 5)
    - Teoría del color, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001156, Folder 6)
    - Teoría - investigación (estilo, género), undated; 1 folder (Box B-001157, Folder 1)
    - Teoría - Walter Benjamin / Mijaíl Bajtín, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001157, Folder 2)
    - Traducción y Arlt, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001157, Folder 3)
    - Transcripciones (Nicolás Sarquís), 1983; 1 folder (Box B-001157, Folder 4)
    - Various Research Topics: Borges, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001174, Folder 1)
    - Various Research Topics: Género / Novela argentina, circa 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box B-001174, Folder 2)
    - Various Research Topics: Ideología, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001174, Folder 3)
    - Various Research Topics: Macedonio Fernández, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001174, Folder 4)
    - Various Research Topics: Modo de apropiación / Ideología / Marx, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001175, Folder 1)
    - Various Research Topics: Traducción, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001175, Folder 2)
    - Various Research Topics: Vanguardia / Las tres vanguardias, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001175, Folder 3)
    - Various Research Topics, undated; 7 folders (Box B-001175, Folder 4, Box B-001176, Folder 1-5, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 4: Notes on Emilio Renzi, 1970-1971; 1 box
    This section contains files relating to Piglia's development of Emilio Renzi; related material may be present in the "Notes about Various Research Topics" section as well.
    - Cartas desde Turín / Emilio, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001158, Folder 1)
    - Renzi, Kramer, Larry, Pavese, Rinaldi (1 of 3), circa 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box B-001158, Folder 2)
    - Renzi, Kramer, Larry, Pavese, Rinaldi (2 of 3), circa 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box B-001158, Folder 3)
    - Renzi, Kramer, Larry, Pavese, Rinaldi (3 of 3), circa 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box B-001158, Folder 4)
    - Various Topics: Emilio Renzi, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001158, Folder 5)
- Series 4: Correspondence, 1953-2016; 3 boxes
  Alphabetically by individual's last name, agency's name, or letter file (A-Z); when last name is not known, letters were sorted by first name or first letter of name. Incomplete letters or letters from unidentified senders where arranged after the alphabetically sorted material.
  This series contains letters and correspondence Ricardo Piglia kept with family, friends, colleagues, publishers, cultrual and educational institutions. Some correspondents signed their letters with nicknames or only first names and these names were preserved in the folder titles in quotations (corrections have been made as new information is received, and folders kept as is, with new information added in parentheses). Piglia kept his correspondence with his employers separately in his teaching files; these files can be found in the corresponding sections in the "Academic Career and Teaching Files" series.
  - A, 1987-1993; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 1)
  - "Andrea", undated; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 2)
  - "Andrés" (Andrés Rivera), 1973-1986; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 3)
  - B, 1964-1996; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 4)
  - Balderston, Daniel, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 5)
  - Berman, Isabel and Antoine Berman, 1985; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 6)
  - Bouthemy, Christian, 1985; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 7)
  - British Medical Journal, 1977; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 8)
  - C, 1993; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 9)
  - "Carmen", 1986; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 10)
  - Cavallari, Hector Mario, 1985; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 11)
  - "China" (Josefina Ludmer), 1980-1985; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 12)
  - The City University of New York, 1986; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 13)
  - Congreso Nacional de Escritores (Universidad Nacional de Tucumán), 1986; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 14)
  - Corbatta, Josefina, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 15)
  - Corporación Eticon C.A., 1976; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 16)
  - Correas, Jaime, 1982; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 17)
  - D, 1987-2016; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 18)
  - De Grandis, Rita, 1991; 1 folder (Box B-001172, Folder 1)
  - "Democracia y Cultura en la Argentina" Symposium, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 19)
  - Díaz Quiñones, Arcadio, 1988-2000; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 20)
  - E, 1992-1999; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 21)
  - Editions W, 1986; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 22)
  - Editorial Celtia, 1986; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 23)
  - Editorial Sudamericana S.A., 1988-1994; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 24)
  - Editorial Tiempo Contemporaneo, 1969; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 25)
  - "Elena", 1976; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 26)
  - "Encuentro Nacional de Literatura y Crítica" (Universidad Nacional del Litoral), 1986; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 27)
  - F, 1987-1992; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 28)
  - Folios Ediciones, S.A., 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 29)
  - Fornet, Jorge, 1993-1996; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 30)
  - Franco, Jean, 1986; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 31)
  - G, 1987-1995; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 32)
  - "Goyo", undated; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 33)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Foundation Fellowship, 1983-1998; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 34)
    Includes one letter from Augusto Roa Bastos dated 1983 to Piglia regarding his candidacy for the Guggenheim Fellowship.
  - H (Héctor Libertella), 1974-2004; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 35)
  - "Hugo" (Hugo Gola), 1991; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 36)
  - I, 1987-2009; 1 folder (Box B-001159, Folder 37)
  - J, 1977-1994; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 1)
  - "John", 1993; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 2)
  - "Juan", 1985-1992; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 3)
  - K, 1992-1994; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 4)
  - L, 1984-1994; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 5)
  - Lara Zavala, Hernan, 1992; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 6)
  - Legrand, Christine, circa 1984; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 7)
  - "Lisandro", 1981; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 8)
  - Ludmer, Josefina, 1982; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 9)
  - M, 1981-2000; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 10)
  - "Mas allá del 'boom': La literatura argentina entre la dictadura y la democracia", 1987; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 11)
  - Minieri, Ramón, 1990; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 12)
  - Ministere de la Culture et de la Communication, 1987; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 13)
  - Moreno-Durán, Rafael Humberto, 1985; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 14)
  - N, 1988-1997; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 15)
  - "Negra", undated; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 16)
  - O'Donnell, Pacho, 1980; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 17)
  - Onetti, Juan Carlos, 1970-1989; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 18)
  - P, 1977-2005; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 19)
  - Pezzoni, Enrique, 1973; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 20)
  - Piglia, Pedro, 1953-1983; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 21)
  - Poirier, José María, 2001; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 22)
  - Premio Literario Casa de las Américas, 1986; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 23)
  - Princeton University, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 24)
  - R, 1987-1994; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 25)
  - "Rafael", undated; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 26)
  - "Riky", 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 27)
  - Riva, Humberto, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 28)
  - "Roque", 1994-1997; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 29)
  - S, 1978-2000; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 30)
  - Saraiva, Arnaldo, 1998; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 31)
  - Sazbón, José, 1973-1984; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 32)
  - "Silvia", undated; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 33)
  - Sociedad Argentina de Escritores, 1981; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 34)
  - Sosa, Teresa, 1981; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 35)
  - Suhrkamp Verlag, 1986; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 36)
  - T, 1994-2011; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 37)
  - "Tatela", circa 1984; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 38)
  - Tcherkaski, Osvaldo, 1976-1982; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 39)
  - V, 1981-1998; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 40)
  - Vlanovsky, Carlos, 1982; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 41)
  - Viñas, David, 1969-1974; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 42)
  - W, 1992; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 43)
  - Waisman, Sergio, 1993-1995; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 44)
  - Weisman, Carlos, 1976; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 45)
  - Y, 1995; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 46)
  - Incomplete Letters Written By Piglia, 1992; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 47)
  - Unidentified Senders, 1975-1994; 1 folder (Box B-001160, Folder 48)
- Series 5: Academic Career and Teaching Files, 1977-2009; 6 boxes
  This series contains Piglia's academic and teaching files. It includes course development notes, course syllabi, occassionally annotated course readers, and administrative files pertaining to his employment at various universities.
  - Subseries 1: Conferences, 1995; 1 box
    Materials relating to various conference Piglia attended or planned during his academic teaching career.
    - "Cómo está hecho el Ulises de Joyce", 1995; 1 folder (Box B-001161, Folder 1)
    - "La ficción argentina" - Conferencia de Ricardo Piglia, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001161, Folder 2)
    - "Poéticas de la novela en América Latina", undated; 1 folder (Box B-001161, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 2: Harvard University, 1989-1990; 1 box
    Contains administrative correspondence and course development notes and syllabi relating to Piglia's teaching career at Harvard University.
    - Administrative File, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box B-001161, Folder 4)
    - Como se construye una historia de la novela - Handwritten Course Development Notes, circa 1990; 1 folder (Box B-001161, Folder 5)
    - Como se construye una historia de la novela - Handwritten Course Development Notes, circa 1990; 1 folder (Box B-001161, Folder 6)
    - Como se construye una historia de la novela - Spanish 294 Syllabus, 1990; 1 folder (Box B-001161, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 3: Princeton University, 1987-2009; 2 boxes
    Contains administrative correspondence and course development notes, course readers, and syllabi relating to Piglia's teaching career at Princeton University.
    - Documentación - Administrative Files, 1987-2008; 1 folder (Box B-001161, Folder 8)
    - El intelectual y los movimientos en América Latina. Imágenes literarias. (Course Syllabi and Development Notes), 1988; 1 folder (Box B-001161, Folder 9)
    - Facundo de D.F. Sarmiento: Historia, política, literatura (Spanish 548 Packet 1), 2004; 1 folder (Box B-001162, Folder 1)
    - La ficción en América Latina: El caso de la novela argentina (Spanish 402 Syllabus), 1987; 1 folder (Box B-001162, Folder 2)
    - Modern Spanish American Literature: La ficción paranoica (Spanish 547 Course Reader), 2005; 1 folder (Box B-001162, Folder 3)
    - Narrative Prose in Latin America - Las tres vanguardias (Spanish 547 Course Readers), 2002-2009; 1 folder (Box B-001162, Folder 4)
    - Sarmiento: Civilización y barbarie. Ideología y literatura. (Spanish 548 Syllabus), 1989-1998; 1 folder (Box B-001162, Folder 5)
    - The Short Story in Latin America (Spanish 331 Syllabus), 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box B-001162, Folder 6)
    - Topics in Spanish American Literature and Ideology (Spanish 345 Course Reader), 1999; 1 folder (Box B-001162, Folder 7)
    - Various Course Syllabi and Development Notes, 1987-1989; 1 folder (Box B-001162, Folder 8)
      Includes materials for the following courses: "La ficción en América Latina: El caso de la novela argentina" (Spanish 402), "El Peronismo en la cultura argentina" (Latin American Studies 401 / Spanish 401); "Como se construye una historia de la novela: El caso argentino" (Spanish 294); "Sarmiento: Civilización y barbarie. Ideología y literatura. (Spanish 548)"; "Las tres vanguardias (Saer, Walsh, Puig)" (Spanish 547).
  - Subseries 4: University of California at Davis, 2000-2001; 1 box
    Contains administrative correspondence and oen syllabus relating to Piglia's teaching career at the University of California at Davis.
    - 20th Century Masters in Spanish-American Literature (Spanish 157 Syllabus and Course Development Notes), undated; 1 folder (Box B-001163, Folder 1)
    - Documentación - Administrative Files, 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box B-001163, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 5: Universidad Nacional de Buenos Aires, 1992-1999; 1 box
    Contains administrative correspondence and course development notes (seminarios), course readers, and syllabi relating to Piglia's teaching career at the Universidad Nacional de Buenos Aires.
    - Administrative Files, 1992-1999; 1 folder (Box B-001163, Folder 3)
    - "Formas breves: Los cuentos de Julio Cortázar", circa 1994; 1 folder (Box B-001163, Folder 4)
    - "Novela y tragedia", circa 1994; 1 folder (Box B-001163, Folder 5)
    - Seminario: "Borges y el género policial", 1996; 1 folder (Box B-001163, Folder 6)
    - Seminario: "Macedonio Fernández: Historia de la novela argentina", 1992; 1 folder (Box B-001163, Folder 7)
    - Seminario: "Roberto Arlt", 1993; 1 folder (Box B-001163, Folder 8)
    - Seminario: "Sarmiento: Historia y literatura", 1998; 1 folder (Box B-001163, Folder 9)
    - Seminario: "Vanguardia y novela (Saer, Puig, Walsh)" - Conversación con Juan José Saer, 1998; 1 folder (Box B-001163, Folder 10)
    - Various Notes Including Seminario: "Política y ficción en Borges" and Seminario: "Borges y la política", 1999; 1 folder (Box B-001163, Folder 11)
    - "Teoría de la novela en Walter Benjamin", circa 1994; 1 folder (Box B-001163, Folder 12)
    - "Teoría del marco", circa 1994; 1 folder (Box B-001163, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 6: Various Course Development and Administrative Matter, 1977-1996; 3 boxes
    This section contains general teaching files. It is unclear which institution Piglia was affiliated with for these materials.
    - Clases, 1987-1996; 1 folder (Box B-001164, Folder 1)
    - Cómo leer la novela argentina - Centro Cultural Ricardo Rojas, 1988; 1 folder (Box B-001164, Folder 2)
    - Course Development: Género / Ideología y literatura, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001164, Folder 3)
    - Curso en filosofía, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001164, Folder 4)
    - Curso en filosofía (Folder 1 of 2), circa 1986; 1 folder (Box B-001164, Folder 5)
    - Curso en filosofía (Folder 2 of 2), circa 1986; 1 folder (Box B-001165, Folder 1)
    - Curso: Las tres vanguardias - Handwritten Notes, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001165, Folder 2)
    - Las tres vanguardias: Programa del curso, 1990; 1 folder (Box B-001165, Folder 3)
    - Sarmiento/Rosas curso (Folder 1 of 2), undated; 1 folder (Box B-001165, Folder 4)
    - Sarmiento/Rosas curso (Folder 2 of 2), undated; 1 folder (Box B-001165, Folder 5)
    - Seminario: Historia de la novela Argentina, 1992; 1 folder (Box B-001166, Folder 1)
    - Seminario: "La ficción paranoica" (Folder 1 of 2), 1991; 1 folder (Box B-001166, Folder 2)
    - Seminario: "La ficción paranoica" (Folder 2 of 2), 1991; 1 folder (Box B-001166, Folder 3)
    - Seminario: "Las tres vanguardias", 1990; 1 folder (Box B-001166, Folder 4)
    - Seminario: "Las tres vanguardias" - Spiral Bound Notebooks (2), 1990; 1 folder (Box B-001166, Folder 5)
    - University of California at San Diego: Administrative File, 1977; 1 folder (Box B-001166, Folder 6)
    - Various Coursework Matter, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001166, Folder 7)
    - Various Coursework Matter - Novela, 1986; 1 folder (Box B-001166, Folder 8)
- Series 6: Photographs and Ephemera, 1959-2010; 2 boxes
  Contains candid and personal family photographs, professionals portraits of Piglia, travel photographs, photographs of other individuals, and collected blank postcards.
  - Subseries 1: Academic Events and Travel, 1972-1996; 1 box
    Alphabetically, by folder title with the exception of the last folder that was added after the initial arrangement.
    Features blank postcards and personal and event photographs relating to academic conferences and Piglia's travels.
    - Blank Postcards, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 1)
    - Conferéncia Borges e a Arte de Narrar, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified Academic and Literary Events, circa 1982-1996; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 3)
    - Travel Photographs: China, circa 1973; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 4)
    - Travel Photographs: Paris, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 5)
    - Travel Ephemera, circa 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2: Family, 1959; 1 box
    Features personal family photographs of Piglia's youth and of his wife, Martha Eguía.
    - Eguía, Martha, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 7)
    - Family Photographs from Ricardo Piglia's Youth, circa 1959; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 8)
    - Piglia, Ricardo and Martha Eguía, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 9)
    - Piglia, Ricardo and Martha Eguía - Gilles Luneau (Photographer), undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 3: Ricardo Piglia, 1979-1993; 2 boxes
    Contains candid and professional portraits of Ricardo Piglia taken by various photographers.
    - Piglia, Ricardo, circa 1980-1986; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 11)
    - Portraits, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 12)
    - Portraits - Alfredo Heer (Photographer), 1993; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 13)
    - Portraits - Daniel Mordzinski (Photographer), undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 14)
    - Portraits - Fiora Bemporad (Photographer), 1981; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 15)
    - Portraits - Gilles Luneau (Photographer), undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 16)
    - Portraits - Grete Stern (Photographer), circa 1979; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 17)
    - Portraits - Juan E. Bustelo (Photographer), undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 18)
    - Portraits - Single Series with Multiple Photographers [?], 1984; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 19)
    - Portraits - Oversize, undated; 1 box (Box P-000100)
  - Subseries 4: Ricardo Piglia With Others, 1963-2010; 1 box
    Alphabetically, by folder title with the exception of the first folder.
    Contains photographs of Ricardo Piglia with other individuals including friends and other writers.
    - Ricardo Piglia with Others, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 20)
    - Babenco, Héctor and Ricardo Piglia, 1997; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 21)
    - Borges, Jorge Luis, Ricardo Piglia, and Others, 1992; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 22)
    - Díaz Quiñones, Arcadio and Ricardo Piglia, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 23)
    - Eguía, Martha, Ricardo Piglia and Others, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 24)
    - Firbas, Paul and Ricardo Piglia, circa 2003-2004; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 25)
    - Piglia, Ricardo and Vasco Pratolini, 1963; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 26)
    - Piglia, Ricardo and Juan José Saer, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 27)
    - Unidentified Individuals with Ricardo Piglia, circa 1963-2010; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 28)
    - Unidentified Individuals with Ricardo Piglia - Julio Menajovsky (Photographer), undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 29)
    - Unidentified Woman with Ricardo Piglia - Grete Stern (Photographer), undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 30)
  - Subseries 5: Other Photographs Without Ricardo Piglia, 1963-2006; 1 box
    These photographs do not feature Ricardo Piglia and feature other individuals, his home or office, locations, or reproductions he kept.
    - Event Poster, 2006; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 31)
    - Home and Office, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 32)
    - Places, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 33)
    - Reproductions of Historical Photographs (1890s) from the Archivo General de la Nación, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 34)
    - Saer, Juan José, circa 1991; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 35)
    - Saer, Juan José and others, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 36)
    - Unidentified Individuals without Ricardo Piglia, circa 1963-1971; 1 folder (Box B-001167, Folder 37)
- Series 7: About Piglia, 1969-2011; 6 boxes
  This series contains materials about Piglia and or his work. It includes awards, health records, interviews (1 audiorecording), and printed material.
  - Subseries 1: Awards, Bibliography, Personal Records, 1973-2008; 2 boxes
    Alphabetically, by folder title starting with awards, then bibliography and personal records thereafter.
    This subseries features awards and degrees Piglia received and includes a print out of his bibliography. There is one folder pertaining to general health records and personal identifications.
    - Fundación Konex - Premios Konex Letras, 2004 September 8; 1 box (Box P-000100)
    - Universidad de Talca - Premio Iberoamericano de Letras "Jose Donoso", 2005 November; 1 box (Box P-000100)
    - Universidad Nacional de La Plata - Reconocimiento, 2008; 1 folder (Box B-001168, Folder 1)
    - Universidad Nacional de Tucumán - Doctor honoris causa, 2001; 1 box (Box P-000100)
    - Universidad Nacional de Tucumán - Doctor honoris causa Letter, 2001; 1 folder (Box B-001168, Folder 2)
    - Bibliography of Publications, undated; 1 folder (Box B-001168, Folder 3)
    - Personal Records, 1973-2005; 1 folder (Box B-001168, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 2: Interviews, 1977-2007; 2 boxes
    This subseries contains various published and unpublished interviews with Ricardo Piglia.
    - "Bianco - Vida 1" (Interview with Piglia and José Bianco), undated; 1 folder (Box B-001168, Folder 5)